SENIOR PRODUCT DESIGNER

Casey Bradford

I am an experienced product designer focused on crafting awesome mobile apps. With 8 years of expertise across visual and product design, I am eager to join a small and collaborative team where I can contribute as a design leader.

Experience

SENIOR PRODUCT DESIGNER AT ZOLA

November 2021 - October 2023

Zola is the leading consumer platform for all things wedding, including websites, registries, invitations, and vendor marketplace. We saw 5.3M monthly unique users.

I led design for Zola's iOS app utilized by 40,000 daily active users and was able to improve the app's onboarding completion by 66%. I spearheaded the launch of key products like the baby registry and wedding budget tool. Additionally, I mentored junior designers, managed the mobile team's component library, and led user research to enhance the Zola web and app home page.

PRODUCT DESIGNER AT CORE

February 2021 - August 2021

AlleyCorp is a venture capital firm that has invested in and built companies such as MongoDB, Gilt Groupe, and Nomad Health. Under AlleyCorp, I worked on a company called Core, which was a marketplace for fitness creators.

I conducted thorough user research, creating innovative 0 to 1 concepts that I presented directly to the board. With a focus on user engagement, I built B2C interfaces for both web and iOS platforms, ensuring a seamless experience across channels.

FREELANCE PRODUCT DESIGNER

January 2020 - current

The Culinistas connects users with private chefs for in-home parties, meal prep and cooking classes. I worked on website rebrand, component library, and enhanced capabilities for booking through the website.

Ellipsis Health uses voice data to identify early signs of anxiety in depression. I worked with the Head of Product to build and test conceptual prototypes for integrations with insurance providers, college campuses, and a mental health app. Our concepts helped Ellipsis secure \$30 million in funding.

CONTACT

925 818-7708
caseyebradford@gmail.com
linkedin.com/in/caseyebradford/
caseybradford.club

EDUCATION

BA in Design Media Arts
UCLA, Class of 2016

UX/UI Bootcamp
DesignLab, 2020

SKILLS

User Research

Usability Testing

Protoyping

Wireframing

Design Systems

Mobile Best Practices

Cross-team Collaboration

Communication

TOOLS

Figma

Usertesting.com

After Effects

GitHub

HTML/CSS

React

Experience continued

FREELANCE PRODUCT DESIGNER CONTINUED

January 2020 - current

Irth is a place for black and brown women to review hospitals and doctors involved in their birthing experiences. I worked to launch the MVP of the app by making UI updates regarding branding and usability.

Other projects include experiences for Six Bells, a store selling country-inspired homewares, Enkasa Homes, a tool for home remodeling, and Drink Lili, a non-alcoholic beverage brand.

DESIGN MANAGER AT FLATIRON SCHOOL (ACQUIRED BY WEWORK)

January 2018 - August 2020

Flatiron School is a coding bootcamp with courses in software engineering, data science, cybersecurity and product design.

As the Design Manager, I led visual communication for ads, collateral, and presentations. I managed two junior designers, collaborated with agencies, and initiated a creative review process. I revitalized the style guide, enhanced photography, and supported 12 new campus launches. I also oversaw the design process for a \$1 million monthly ad budget, surpassing campaign goals through creative optimization in imagery and copy.

ART DIRECTOR AT VAYNERMEDIA

August 2016 - August 2017

VaynerMedia is a digital agency specializing in social media strategy. During my time there I was dedicated to the Chase Sapphire business. I helped plan and execute video and photo shoots to create assets for paid social campaigns and regularly presented work to clients.

INTERESTS

Sewing my own clothing
Cooking my way through
Treasures of the Mexican Table
Trying every sake bar in NYC
Perfecting my drift in Mario Kart
Traveling to new places